Nazarii Pyndus

Front End Engineer

Email: npundus@gmail.com

Skype: npundus

Profile

Front End Web Developer with over 3 years of commercial experience in software development using Angular Framework. Familiarized with cross-device responsive web development. Result-orientated, responsible and attention to detail.

Technical Skills

Category	Skill list
Programming languages	JavaScript , TypeScript
Operating systems	Windows, Ubuntu, MacOS, Android
Libraries	Angular Material ,AngularJS Material , ZingChart, Angular Bootstrap , UI-Cropper, Angular Paging , Angular Translate, RxJs, Lodash, Sweetalert, ngxtranslate, Moment, Moment-timezone, ng-color, ng-pick-datatime, ngx-mat-select-search, Chart.js,angular-calendar,date-fns, bootstrap 4, Jquery, Google maps,Formspree, Ngrx, Formspree, Bootstrap
Technologies	Angular 2 +, AngularJS, Ionic 4+
Development tools	Google DevTools, Avocode, Figma, WebStorm, VS Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Android Studio, Gulp
RDBMS	SQL
Web	HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JADE, PUG, FTL
SCM	Git, GitLab, Github
BTS	Redmine, Trello, Jira, Gitlab board

Education

2017 - 2021

Ivano-Frankivsk National Technical University of Oil and Gas Bachelor's degree Automation and computer-integration technologies, system engineer

Ivano-Frankivsk, Ukraine

Languages

- English—Intermediate
- Russian— Advanced
- Ukrainian— Native

Working experience

October 2018 – present Ivano Frankivsk, Ukraine

Dates: 5 May – 3 September 2021

Role: Angular Developer

About project: Admin site for trading app

Description: Designing and developing, mobile responsive, admin system developing of managing

trading platform

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 11, Google DevTools, Avocode,

Dates: 25 February 2020 - 15 May 2020

Role: JS Developer

Description: Designing and developing, mobile responsive

Development tools and Technologies: TPL, Gulp, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript

Dates: 28 January - 4 September 2021

Role: Angular Developer

About project: Service for viewing real estate for sale on the map and infrastructure

Description: Designing and developing, mobile responsive, new Google Maps features, data content

creating (no backend), mail send

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 9, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm,

Formspree

Dates: 20 January 2021 – 1 September 2021

Role: Ionic Developer

About project: Stake analytic app for IOS/Android with managing readiness

Description: Creating builds, new design, new features

Development tools and Technologies: Android Studio, Mobile debug, Google DevTools,

WebStorm

Dates: 17 February - 25 February 2021

Role: JS Developer

About project: Landing page for sport brand

Description: Designing and developing, mobile responsive

Development tools and Technologies: PUG, Gulp, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Google DevTools

Dates: 8 January 2021 - 15 January 2021

Role: Angular Developer

Description: Creating new pages, new design

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 10, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm

Dates: 24 December 2020 - 9 February 2021

Role: Angular Developer

About project: Questionnaires which helps companies and individuals create healthier working

environments

Description: Write TypeScript, writing custom: services, pipes ,modal windows,

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 7, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm

Dates: 5 January 2020 - May 2020

Role: Front-End Developer

About project: Service of booking permits

Description: Write TypeScript, redesign Pages, bug fixing

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 8, Google DevTools, Figma, WebStorm

Dates: 5 January 2020 - May 2020

Role: Front-End Developer

About project: Admin panel of management light (lamp) in buildings/floors/rooms/zones by

scheduler, RGBA/Bright of light.

Description: Write TypeScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes ,modal windows, mobile responsive, creating Calendar events for Smart House, Color Picker

RGB, custom for Warm Cold picker, bug fixing

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 8, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm

Dates: 13 November 2018 - 4 January 2021

Role: Front-End Developer

About project: Several web sites (service), with ability to configure and buy 2D/3D models of

furniture. Plugin iframe in customer site

Description: Change design and write or rewrite JavaScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes ,modal windows, Iframe plugins, mobile responsive, working with Unity (web version), bug fixing

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 8, Angular 11, AngularJS, Google DevTools , Avocode , WebStorm